http://www.selectbs.com/general-information/privacystatement

Contact UsAbout UsManagementTrademarkPrivacyLegal
HomeProductsApplication Development ToolsSelect Solution FactorySelect Asset ManagerSelect Business ModelerSelect Process Director PlusSelect PerspectiveSelect SSADMSelect YourdonSelect VideosMainframe ToolsUltraquest ReporterUltraQuest LibraryUltraQuest ApplicationsUltraQuest GatewayUltraQuest WebservicesNOMADTransit ETLUltraQuest Cloud ServerSolutionsApplication Development SolutionsAnalysis and DesignProcess MaturityComponent ReuseAcademic SupportMainframe SolutionsApplication ManagementData ManagementDecision SupportIntegration and ReportingMainframe ReportingWeb-enabling ApplicationsWeb Based ReportingWeb ServicesXML for Data ExchangeSectorsETL SolutionServicesConsultancyEducationTraining CoursesApplication Development ToolsMainframe ToolsSupportNOMAD/UltraQuest Support EnglishNOMAD/UltraQuest Support FrançaisApplication Development Tools SupportPartnersCustomers and Case StudiesDownloadsVideosNews and Social MediaPress ReleasesNewslettersSocial Media
Legal Information: Privacy Statement
Legal Information: Privacy Statement Select Business Solutions, Inc. (“Select”) prides itself on revolutionizing the way organizations better manage their projects. In pursuit of that goal, we respect and protect the privacy of those who visit our web site. This privacy statement outlines five principles in accordance with worldwide practices for customer privacy and data protection followed by Select. Thus, we want to give you the comfort and confidence you need to fully participate in our online offerings so that we can better serve your needs.
Because of the nature of our products and business, our web sites are not designed to appeal to children under the age of 13. Therefore, we don’t knowingly attempt to solicit or receive any information from children.
1. Notice
Throughout our web site there may be occasions when we will ask you for information that personally identifies you (Personal Information) or allows us to contact you. Generally this information is requested when you are asked to register before receiving/downloading free software, multi-media product demonstrations, employment applications or under other various circumstances such as occasional special promotions or contests.
2. Consent
If you simply want to browse, you do not have to register or provide personal information, and you can still use most of the site. But you will not be able to access any areas which require registration. For those browsing rest assured you can surf with confidence knowing that we do not use cookies in any part of our site. The Selectbs.com web site may provide links to third party sites, such as those of our business partners or distributors. Select is not responsible for the actions of these third parties as they retain total control over their web site. You should review their privacy policy to learn more about what and how they collect and use private information.
3. Access
We will provide you with the opportunity to update or ensure that your personal information is correct and current by calling our corporate headquarters.
4. Security
We work to protect personally identifiable information from unauthorized access using commercially available computer security products, such as firewalls, as well as carefully developed security procedures and practices. All employees must review and sign these practices which include limiting access to sensitive information only to those employees who require the information. With these measures, Selectbs.com strictly protects the security of your personal information to keep us from using or sharing the information you provide for purposes other than to fulfill your request or specific intended use. We carefully protect your data from loss, misuse, unauthorized access or disclosure, alteration or destruction. We do not sell or otherwise have secondary uses of private information you provide regardless of how such information is gathered.
5. Enforcement
If for some reason you believe Selectbs.com has not adhered to these principles, please contact us and ask for the legal department, and we will do our best to determine and correct any problem promptly. To ensure your request is properly addressed be sure to identify your problem as a privacy policy issue.
:: What's New
Coronavirus Update
Read Select's Announcement
Select AnnouncesNOMAD 8.00 for z/OS
Read about Select's new release ofNOMAD for z/OS
Select AnnouncesNOMAD 8.00 for z/VM
Read about Select's new release ofNOMAD for z/VM
Peek at UltraQuest 6.0
Select AnnouncesHadoop integration initiativefor Transit ETL product line
© Copyright 1988-2020, Select Business Solutions, Inc.
Sitemap
